It's human nature to want to play.
爱玩是人的天性。
From board games to sports, games have been an integral part of human culture since time immemorial.
从桌面游戏到体育运动，游戏自古以来就是人类文化中不可或缺的一部分。
Since their invention in the mid-20th century, video games have been among the most popular pastimes.
自20世纪中期电子游戏诞生以来，它就跻身最受欢迎的消遣方式之列。
In fact, in 2018 UK gamers spent on average over seven hours a week playing, according to market research conducted by global network provider Limelight.
全球网络服务提供商Limelight开展的市场调研显示，2018年英国玩家平均每周的游戏时长超过7小时。
But how much is too much?
但玩多久才算过度？
When does entertainment become an addiction?
娱乐何时会演变成成瘾？
Are we hooked on video games?
我们是否已经对电子游戏上瘾了？
'The urge to play never goes away,' said Sean – not his real name - on the BBC's Victoria Derbyshire programme.
在英国广播公司的《维多利亚·德比郡》节目中，化名肖恩的男子表示：“想要玩游戏的冲动从未消失。”
His fixation with gaming once involved playing for 48 hours straight.
他曾经对游戏极度痴迷，有一次连续玩了48个小时。
It consumed him to the point he would ignore his family and children and ended up losing them along with his job and home.
游戏占据了他的全部生活，他开始忽视家人和孩子，最终不仅失去了家庭，还丢了工作、没了住所。
Since then he has checked into rehab, and despite falling off the wagon once or twice, he has been on track for the last 14 months.
从那以后，他住进了康复中心接受治疗，期间虽然有过一两次故态复萌，但在过去的14个月里，他没有继续沉沦于游戏。
'Sean' is not alone.
像肖恩这样的人并非个例。
The UK Addiction Treatment group have noticed an increase in the number of people seeking treatment for gaming addiction from four in 2014 to 22 in 2018, they told the BBC.
英国成瘾治疗中心向英国广播公司透露，寻求游戏成瘾治疗的人数从2014年的4人增长到了2018年的22人。
And in 2018 the World Health Organization classified gaming addiction as a disorder.
2018年，世界卫生组织将游戏成瘾列为一种精神障碍。
In the UK, an enquiry into technology addiction held by the Digital, Culture, Media and Sport Select Committee included testimony from self-professed gaming addicts.
在英国，数字、文化、媒体和体育特别委员会针对科技成瘾问题开展了调查，其中纳入了多名自称游戏成瘾者的证词。
One, Matus Mikus, said "games by their very nature are addictive."
马图斯·米库斯就是其中之一，他表示“游戏本质上就具有成瘾性”。
However, the association for UK Interactive Entertainment informed the committee that there was a 'lack of evidence' around the addiction.
然而，英国互动娱乐协会却向该委员会表示，目前关于游戏成瘾的“证据不足”。
They stated that gaming could be a 'force for good, encouraging, among other things, critical thinking skills'.
该协会称，游戏可以成为一种“有益的力量”，除了能培养人的批判性思维能力，还有其它好处。
Indeed, in a 2018 BBC article, registrar in anaesthetic and intensive care at Sheffield Teaching Hospital, Rajin Chowdhury seems to agree.
2018年英国广播公司的一篇报道中，谢菲尔德教学医院的麻醉与重症监护科住院医生拉金·乔杜里似乎也认同这一观点。
Gaming, he says, made him more dextrous, improved hand-eye coordination and aided procedures that were performed remotely through looking at a screen, especially where the surgery controls were not intuitive.
他表示，玩游戏让他的手脚变得更灵活，提升了手眼协调能力，并且有助于他完成那些需要对着屏幕远程操作的辅助医疗程序，尤其是在手术控制设备操作不太方便的情况下。
Are video games addictive?
电子游戏真的会让人上瘾吗？
It's unclear.
目前尚无定论。
Like anything, moderation is key.
和任何事物一样，适度是关键。
The games themselves may not be the problem, but letting them negatively impact our lives certainly is.
游戏本身或许并非问题所在，但如果让它对我们的生活产生负面影响，那就确实成了问题。
With that in mind, play well, have fun and don't forget to take regular breaks.
牢记这一点，尽情享受游戏的乐趣，但别忘了定时休息。